本字幕由YYeTs人人影视原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译： 萌Su  泽川  樱桃橙子  噎死青春  胡七七  enddd3d
翻译： 熊孩子  hammer_tank  Vitaminwater  Mondo  Chique
翻译： 风吹日落  海伦  小囧子  草莓花  擦擦  shark  七七布
校对： 天朝直属  Xtina  往兮  草莓花  送小孩  DayDreaming  妞儿
时间轴： 草鱼禾枣苗  擦擦  贝贝  JimmyBeck  子衿  迟迟
后期： 孤帆      总监： 往兮   草莓花
人人影视-韩剧精灵倾情支持
来自洛杉矶的现场直播
欢迎收看《第40届全美音乐大奖》
女士们先生们
欢迎Usher
♪They say life is a battlefield♪
♪I say bring it on♪
♪If you wanna know how I feel♪
♪Leave it till it's gone♪
♪I'm just saying that what don't kill♪
♪Only makes you strong♪
♪If you don't recognize what is real♪
♪Then forever is a long, long...♪
♪Time, some things never change here we go again♪
♪Feel like I'm losing my mind♪
♪Shake it off, then you go♪
♪I don't care anymore♪
♪Just go numb♪
♪You never know until you let go♪
♪Let's go numb♪
♪I can feel you now♪
♪You say it's better if we♪
♪Love each other separately♪
♪I just need you one more time♪
♪I can't get what we had out of my mind♪
♪Where are you now♪
♪When I need you around♪
♪I'm on my knees but it seems we're♪
♪Going nowhere fast we've reached the climax♪
♪We're together now we're undone♪
♪Won't commit so♪
♪I gave my best, it wasn't enough♪
♪You came and said we argue too much♪
♪We made a mess of what used to be love♪
♪So why do I care, I care♪
♪At all♪
♪I can't stop won't stop♪
♪Usher baby♪
♪Yeah, will you do it again♪
♪Can't stop♪
♪Hey, what's up♪
♪This is my jam♪
♪Turn it up♪
♪Play it loud in the club♪
♪There's this fire♪
♪You're burning me up♪
♪Oh girl, yeah girl♪
♪I've been looking♪
♪Around the world♪
♪And right when I saw you♪
♪I fell in love♪
♪And I want you forever, and ever, and ever♪
♪Cause I can't, can't, stop it♪
♪I can't, can't, stop it♪
♪I can't stop won't stop♪
♪Can't stop won't stop♪
♪Girl you are my sugar shot♪
♪Love you like a lollipop♪
♪From the bottom to the top♪
♪I'ma get you wet, raincoat♪
♪Let me be your body soap♪
♪Up and down, rollercoaster♪
♪We can love forever♪
♪You can call me papa♪
♪Girl you my freaky mama♪
♪Mami be my data♪
♪Work on my body girl♪
♪Oh yeah right now I pour it on me whenever♪
♪Your my sexy apparatea♪
♪You can't stop now♪
♪Won't stop now♪
♪Don't stop now♪
♪Keep it going now♪
♪Drop it ooh now♪
♪Can't stop won't stop♪
♪Hey, what's up♪
♪This is my jam♪
♪Turn it up♪
♪Play it loud in the club♪
♪There's this fire♪
♪You're burning me up♪
♪Oh girl, yeah girl♪
♪I've been looking♪
♪Around the world♪
♪And right when I saw you♪
♪I fell in love♪
♪And I want you forever, and ever, and ever♪
♪Cause I can't, can't, stop it♪
♪I can't, can't, stop it♪
♪I can't stop won't stop♪
这里是洛杉矶诺基亚剧院
第40届全美音乐大奖
《第40届全美音乐大奖》直播现场
今晚的表演嘉宾有
AMA辉煌时刻中将出现的有
接下来掌声有多才多艺的
Ryan Seacrest
谢谢大家
欢迎来到这个特别的夜晚
我们在此庆祝这一里程碑
那就是第40届全美音乐大奖
现在全世界有超过190个国家
在观看这个颁奖典礼
今晚  我们将回顾过去40年中
全美音乐奖的精彩瞬间
现在  我们先来回顾一下
来自Beyonce的经典演出
一起来看看
♪I got gloss on my lips♪
♪A man on my hips♪
AMA辉煌时刻
♪Got me tighter than my Dereon jeans♪
♪Acting up, drink in my cup♪
♪I could care less what you think♪
♪I need no permission, did I mention♪
♪Don't pay him any attention♪
♪'Cause you had your turn♪
♪But now you gonna learn♪
♪What it really feels like to miss me♪
♪Cause if you liked it then you should have put a ring on it♪
♪If you liked it then you shoulda put a ring on it♪
♪Don't be mad once you see that he want it♪
歌名《All The Single Ladies》的中文意思为"单身小妞"
那就是Beyonce和单身小妞们
今晚晚些时候  我会回到这里
美国著名电视人
向Dick Clark致敬
千万不要错过
现在  请允许我揭晓
今晚第一个奖项
"流行/摇滚类最受欢迎男歌手奖"
第40届全美音乐大奖的
第一个奖项将花落谁家
一起来看看
以下是
"流行/摇滚类最受欢迎男歌手奖"提名
今晚  获得第40届全美音乐大奖
第一项大奖的是
Justin Bieber
这是Justin Bieber的第五个
全美音乐大奖
他曾在2010年获得过此类别的奖项
他今晚还有两项提名
谢谢你们
流行/摇滚类最受欢迎男歌手
非常感谢  首先  我想说
我想说  这奖是给所有讨厌我的人
他们认为我只是昙花一现
但我相信我会经久不衰
第二  我想谢谢我的妈妈
她就坐在那儿
她很棒  很美丽
我想谢谢坐在那的Scooter Brown
你是位优秀的导师
是我所尊敬的榜样
感谢我的家人
以及所有美得冒泡的粉丝
你们真是太不可思议了
我爱你们
最后一件事
我也爱你
我爱你们
谢谢你们  就这样吧
爱你们
接下来  Carly Rea Jepsen
和The Wanted即将出场
稍后  还有Justin Bieber
Ke$ha和Kelly Clarkson登台
Psy和神秘嘉宾将带来
国际热单《江南Style》
谁又将赢得
"乡村类最受欢迎女歌手奖"
是Carrie  是Taylor
还是Miranda呢
ABC稍后为您揭晓
ABC台《第40届全美音乐大奖》
由"Old Navy  世界上最有爱的航海"
以及"Cheer Magedoon  欢乐就在身边"赞助播出
欢迎回到《第40届全美音乐大奖》
有请艾美奖获得者
来自《摩登家庭》剧组的
Eric Stonestreet
大家晚上好
我也有点乡村风呢
真的吗  我还很摇滚呢  Eric
我的天呐
我简直是个全能主持人
我能颁发
"成人时代最受欢迎歌手"啦
"另类摇滚最受欢迎歌手"啦
"嘻哈最佳专辑"啦  随便你说一个
但是今年制作方让我颁发
"乡村类最受欢迎女歌手"
简直像中头彩了
说到赢家
这三位女歌手中的一位
即将获得全美音乐大奖
请看短片
以下是
"乡村类最受欢迎女歌手"提名
还有  顺便一说
今晚公布获奖的时候
不会再有装着获奖名单的信封了
因为获奖人的名字
将会出现在这台
三星Galaxy Note II上
糟糕  没人看到上面的名字吧
获得全美音乐大奖的是
还没出现呢  有了
Taylor Swift
这是Taylor Swift连续五年
获得该项殊荣
目前为止  她已获得
11项全美音乐大奖
Taylor  你之前获过奖吗
给你吧
- 我太激动了  - 我帮你拿着
好的  谢谢
谢谢大家
这简直太不真实了
谢谢我的歌迷
乡村类最受欢迎女歌手
是你们为我投的票
这几周我的专辑《Red》刚出来
你们是我坚强的后盾
我刚把巡演的时间定下
你们就已经买光了所有门票
我太震惊了
我想我要说的是
我现在非常非常开心
这都是因为有你们
谢谢你们为我投票
我爱你们
AMA辉煌时刻
有请我的妹妹  Janet Jackson
她参演了ABC热播家庭剧《美少女的谎言》
他的专辑《Home》荣登榜首
有请Lucy Hale和Phillip Phillips
2012年风靡全球的国际突破单曲之一
出自于一位加拿大的歌手
她的这首歌红遍大街小巷
大家纷纷在YouTube上分享了自己的演绎
她的新单曲叫《This Kiss》
她就是Carly Rae Jepsen
♪I went out last night♪
♪I'm going out tonight again♪
♪Anything to capture your attention (your attention)♪
♪And she's a real sweet girl♪
♪And you know I got a boy♪
♪Details we both forgot to mention (forgot to mention)♪
♪And you, I always know where you are♪
♪And you always know where I am♪
♪We're taking it way too far♪
♪But I don't want it to end♪
♪This kiss is something I can't resist♪
♪Your lips are undeniable♪
♪This kiss is something I can't risk♪
♪Your heart is unreliable♪
♪Something so sentimental♪
♪You make so detrimental♪
♪And I wish it didn't feel like this♪
♪Cause I don't wanna miss this kiss♪
♪But if you ask me to, I couldn't, I couldn't, I♪
♪You're leaning closer and I shouldn't, I shouldn't, I♪
♪I shouldn't, I shouldn't, I♪
♪I don't wanna miss this kiss♪
好啦  会唱的一起唱哦
♪I threw a wish in the well♪
♪Don't ask me, I'll never tell♪
♪I looked to you as it fell♪
♪And now you're in my way♪
♪I'd trade my soul for a wish♪
♪Pennies and dimes for a kiss♪
♪I wasn't looking for this♪
♪But now you're in my way♪
♪Your stare was holdin'♪
♪Ripped jeans, skin was showin'♪
♪Hot night, wind was blowin'♪
♪Where you think you're going, baby♪
♪Hey, I just met you♪
♪And this is crazy♪
♪But here's my number♪
♪So call me, maybe♪
♪It's hard to look right♪
♪At you baby♪
♪But here's my number♪
♪So call me, maybe♪
♪Hey, I just met you♪
♪And this is crazy♪
♪But here's my number♪
♪So call me, maybe♪
♪And all the other boys♪
♪Try to chase me♪
♪But here's my number♪
♪So call me, maybe♪
♪Before you came into my life♪
♪I missed you so bad♪
♪I missed you so, so bad♪
♪Before you came into my life♪
♪I missed you so bad♪
♪And you should know that♪
♪I missed you so, so bad♪
♪Bad, bad, bad♪
♪It's hard to look right♪
♪At you baby♪
♪But here's my number♪  一起来
♪(So call me, maybe)♪
♪Hey, I just met you♪
♪And this is crazy♪
♪But here's my number♪
♪So call me, maybe♪
♪And all the other boys♪
♪Try to chase me♪
♪But here's my number♪
♪So call me, maybe♪
♪Before you came into my life♪
♪I missed you so bad♪
♪I missed you so, so bad♪
♪Before you came into my life♪
♪I missed you so bad♪
♪And you should know that♪
♪So call me, maybe♪
男孩组合再次流行
今天我们请到了最火爆的组合之一
有请The Wanted
♪She wants me to come over♪
♪I can tell her eyes don't lie♪
♪She's calling me in the dark♪
♪She moves us around the room♪
♪Where the lights turn like the sky♪
♪Confidence like a rock star♪
♪I wanna put my hands on her hands♪
♪Feel the heat from her skin♪
♪Get reckless in the starlight♪
♪I'm moving to the beat of her heart♪
♪I was so lost until tonight, tonight♪
♪I found you, in the darkest hour♪
♪I found you, in a pouring rain♪
♪I found you, when I was on my knees♪
♪And your love pulled me back again♪
♪Found you in a river of pure emotions♪
♪I found you, my only truth♪
♪I found you, with the music playing♪
♪I was lost♪
♪Til I found you, you, you♪
♪The night is getting colder♪
♪And I can't come off this high♪
♪I don't want this here to end♪
♪I know she feels the same♪
♪Cause I can see it in her eyes♪
♪She says can we start again♪
♪I wanna put my hands on her hands♪
♪Feel the heat from her skin♪
♪Get reckless in the starlight♪
♪She's moving to the beat of my heart♪
♪We were so lost until tonight, tonight♪
♪I found you, in the darkest hour♪
♪I found you, in a pouring rain♪
♪I found you, when I was all in need♪
♪And your love pulled me back again♪
♪Found you in a river of pure emotions♪
♪I found you, my only truth♪
♪I found you, with the music playing♪
♪I was lost♪
♪Til I found you, you, you♪
♪I said, people♪
♪We're all looking for love tonight♪
♪But sometimes we can't see it♪
♪We're blinded by light♪
♪And we all get low, all get low♪
♪Searching for that piece of mind♪
♪Just when I've given up♪
♪Looking for some kind inside♪
♪That's when I found you, you, you♪
全美观众嗨起来
♪I found you, in the darkest hour♪
♪I found you, in a pouring rain♪
♪I found you, when I was all in need♪
♪And your love pulled me back again♪
♪Found you in a river of pure emotions♪
♪I found you, my only truth♪
♪I found you, with the music playing♪
♪I was lost♪
♪Til I found you♪
谢谢大家
今夜  获奖名单将在
三星Galaxy Note II手机上展现
接下来  Kelly Clarkson将登台
精彩不容错过
还将颁发"说唱/嘻哈最佳专辑"奖
精彩尽在《第40届全美音乐大奖》
ABC台《第40届全美音乐大奖》
由三星Galaxy Note II手机赞助播出
开启手机新纪元
这里是洛杉矶诺基亚影剧院
欢迎继续收看《第40届全美音乐大奖》
有请著名音乐人  获奖制作人
Randy Jackson
首先我想向在东海岸
受飓风"桑迪"影响的同胞们
表达最诚挚的问候
大家都献出一份爱心吧
详情请登陆redcross.org/abc
好的  下一位表演嘉宾
她充满着正能量
这姑娘真心令人爱不释手
我到现在还记得
第一次听到她声音的感觉
真不敢相信  十年都过去了
现在还出了张精选集
我的天呐
掌声有请大家最爱的
为大家带来热单串烧的
KC是以美国偶像第一季冠军的身份出道的  因为是出道以来热单回顾  这里特地找了三个人扮评委
Kelly Clarkson
♪Miss Independent♪
♪Miss self-sufficient♪
♪Miss keep your distance ♪
♪Miss unafraid♪
♪Miss out of my way♪
♪Miss don't let a man interfere, no♪
♪Miss on her own♪
♪Miss almost grown♪
♪Miss never let a man help her off her throne♪
♪So, by keeping her heart protected♪
♪She'd never ever feel rejected♪
♪Little miss apprehensive♪
♪Said ooh, she fell in love♪
♪Here's the thing we started off friends♪
♪It was cool but it was all pretend♪
大家一起来
♪And all you'd ever hear me say♪
♪Is how I pictured me with you♪
♪That's all you'd ever hear me say♪
♪But since u been gone♪
♪I can breathe for the first time♪
♪I'm so movin on yeah yeah♪
♪Thanks to you♪
♪Now I get♪
♪What I want♪
♪Since u been gone♪
大家跟我一起唱
♪Thanks to you I got a new thing started♪
♪Thanks to you I'm not the broken hearted♪
♪Thanks to you I'm finally thinking about me♪
♪You know in the end the day you left was just my beginning♪
♪In the end♪
♪What doesn't kill you makes you stronger♪
♪Stand a little taller♪
♪Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone♪
♪What doesn't kill you makes a fighter♪
♪Footsteps even lighter♪
♪Doesn't mean I'm over cause you're gone♪
♪What doesn't kill you makes you stronger' stronger♪
♪Just me' myself and I♪
♪What doesn't kill you makes you stronger♪
♪Stand a little taller♪
♪Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone♪
♪When I'm alone♪
♪I don't wanna be left behind♪
♪Distance was a friend of mine♪
♪Catching breath in a web of lies♪
♪I've spent most of my life♪
♪Riding waves, playing acrobat♪
♪Shadowboxing the other half♪
♪Learning how to react♪
♪I've spent most of my time♪
♪Catching my breath, letting it go♪
♪Turning my cheek for the sake of the show♪
♪Now that you know, this is my life♪
♪I won't be told what's supposed to be right♪
♪Catch my breath♪
♪No one can hold me back♪
♪I ain't got time for that♪
♪Catch my breath♪
♪Won't let them get me down♪
♪It's all so simple now♪
欢迎演员兼主持人
以及唱片制作人兼音乐人
Stacy Keibler以及Ne-Yo
《全美音乐大奖》1974年首播时
嘻哈说唱还是比较罕见的
然而世易时移
1989年音乐奖首次设说唱专项奖
第一张获此殊荣的专辑是
《He's the DJ, I'm the Rapper》
来自DJ Jazzy Jeff和The Fresh Prince
Will Smith是DJ Jazzy Jeff乐队的成员
因Will Smith而名声鹊起
一起来看看提名名单
"说唱/嘻哈最佳专辑"
提名的有
"说唱/嘻哈最佳专辑"  获奖的是...
Nicki Minaj
这是Nicki Minaj第三次折桂全美音乐奖
去年她也斩获此奖
大家好
非常感谢各位
说唱/嘻哈类最受欢迎歌手
Nicki女粉丝们的自称
谢谢我漂亮的Barb们
虽然我不知你们身在何处
但是谢谢你们的投票
谢谢一直以来对我的支持
感谢上帝赐予我出唱片的机会
你们太好了
我想感谢Kenny  Piro和Robinson
小Wayne  Cash Money以及环球唱片
感谢大家
感谢跟我合作的所有艺人
谢谢你们
两度夺得"流行/摇滚类"全美音乐奖
有请这位畅销书作家  百老汇作曲家
Cyndi Lauper
她是位国际超级巨星
今年流行乐风潮复苏她功不可没
我很荣幸请出这位女星
为我们演唱今年她的最热单曲
有请Ke$ha
♪I hear your heart beat♪
♪To the beat of the drums♪
♪Oh what a shame that♪
♪You came here with someone♪
♪So while you're here in my arms♪
♪Let's make the most of the night♪
♪Like we're gonna die young♪
♪We're gonna die young♪
♪Let's make the most of the night♪
♪Like we're gonna die young♪
♪Hearts, out of minds♪
♪Running till we out of time♪
♪Wild childs, looking good♪
♪Living hard, just like we should♪
♪Don't care who's watching♪
♪When we tearing up♪
♪You know♪
♪That magic that we got♪
♪That nobody can touch♪
♪You show♪
♪Looking for some trouble tonight♪
♪Take my hand♪
♪I'll show you the wild side♪
♪Like it's the♪
♪Last night of our lives♪
♪We'll keep dancing 'till we die♪
♪I hear your heart beat♪
♪To the beat of the drums♪
♪Oh what a shame that♪
♪You came here with someone♪
♪So while you're here in my arms♪
♪Let's make the most of the night♪
♪Like we're gonna die young♪
♪We're gonna die young♪
♪Let's make the most of the night♪
♪Like we're gonna die young♪
♪Punks, taking shots♪
♪Stripping down to dirty socks♪
♪Music up, getting hot♪
♪Kiss me, give me all you got♪
♪It's pretty obvious♪
♪That you got a crush♪
♪You know♪
♪That magic in your pants♪
♪Is making me blush♪
♪You show♪
♪Looking for some trouble tonight♪
♪Take my hand♪
♪I'll show you the wild side♪
♪Like it's the last♪
♪Night of our lives♪
♪We'll keep dancing 'till we die♪
♪Like we're gonna die young♪
♪I hear your heart beat to the beat of the drums(wow wow)♪
♪Oh what a shame that you came here with someone(someone)♪
♪So while you're here in my arms♪
♪Let's make the most of the night♪
♪Like we're gonna die young♪
您为哪位新人投票了呢
年度新人/组合
"Old Navy年度新人/组合"即将揭晓
谁能摘得大奖呢
J.Cole  Fun  Gotye
Carly Rae Jepsen
还是One Direction呢
接下来  No Doubt即将登台
还有Pink  Justin Bieber
联手Nicki Minaj的精彩演出
更有Stevie Wonder向Dick Clark致敬的演出
"乡村类最受欢迎男歌手奖"
会是Jason Aldean
Luke Bryan还是Eric Church呢
精彩尽在ABC台《第40届全美音乐大奖》
由全新道奇Dart二代赞助
Dart  新领航
有请刚刚订婚的人气情侣组合
Karmin
他们曾是一支来自
加利福尼亚州阿纳海姆市的本土乐队
现在他们的音乐风靡全球
唱功与外貌皆备
有请魅力逼人的No Doubt
♪Go ahead and look at me♪
♪'Cause that's what I want(That's what I want)♪
♪Take a good look won't you please♪
♪I know you wanna stare♪
♪You can't help it and I don't care(Don't care)♪
♪So look at me♪
♪'Cause that's what I want(That's what I want)♪
♪Do you think I'm looking hot♪
♪Do you think this hits the spot♪
♪How is this looking on me, looking on me♪
♪Do you think I'm looking hot♪
♪Do you think this hits the spot♪
♪How is this looking on me, looking on me♪
♪Go ahead and stare♪
♪And take a picture please if you need♪
♪And I think that says it all♪
♪Chasing it, I don't know why♪
♪I think about it a lot(About it a lot)♪
♪Better hurry, running out of time♪
♪I can't tell anymore♪
♪I don't know what I'm looking for(Looking for)♪
♪You know what I mean(What I mean)♪
♪I think about it a lot(About it a lot)♪
♪Do you think I'm looking hot♪
♪Do you think this hits the spot♪
♪How is this looking on me, looking on me♪
♪Do you think I'm looking hot♪
♪Do you think this hits the spot♪
♪How is this looking on me, looking on me♪
♪Go ahead and stare♪
♪And take a picture please if you need♪
♪And I think that says it all♪
♪Boom♪
♪Boom Boom♪
♪Boom(Boom)♪
♪Running on empty but I have had plenty♪
♪You're complimentary, but I'm just pretending♪
♪Uniform, hide behind there, this is my diversion♪
♪Go ahead and stare on my ragamuffin♪
♪Feeling so fake it, I bait it you take it♪
♪One eye in the mirror, put on my veneer♪
♪Could have sworn, it's a sure shot♪
♪Are you onto my con♪
♪Go ahead and stare, I'm a ragamuffin♪
♪Boom Boom♪
一起来
♪Do you think I'm looking hot♪
♪Do you think this hits the spot♪
♪How is this looking on me, looking on me♪
♪Do you think I'm looking hot♪
♪Do you think this hits the spot♪
♪How is this looking on me, looking on me♪
♪Go ahead and stare♪
♪And take a picture please, if you need♪
♪And I think that says it all♪
一起来
♪Do you think I'm looking hot♪
♪Do you think I'm looking hot ♪
♪Do you think I'm looking hot hot♪
有请出演《丑闻》的Kerry Washington
及《与星共舞》的Apolo Anton Ohno
有人称之为另类
也有人称之为潮流
不管怎样  它碉堡就是了
请看提名名单
"另类摇滚最受欢迎歌手"
提名者有
"另类摇滚最受欢迎歌手"获奖的是...
Linkin Park
这是Linkin Park第五次赢下该奖
在03  04  07和08年他们都获得此奖
在此我们要感谢Michael Green
John Brilliam  Rand Martin等
另类摇滚最受欢迎歌手
以及TSO  David Landian的团队
华纳兄弟唱片公司  Machine Shop
我们的朋友  家人
我们的公关Kim
我看看还有谁忘了说...
巡回演出的工作人员
最重要的是  我们的"林肯地下粉丝团"
还有所有为我们投票的粉丝
你们是世界上最好的粉丝
非常感谢大家
接下来
Taylor Switf将带来新单
随后登场的有Pitbull  Justin Bieber
Nicki Minaj以及跳"江南Style"鸟叔
另外Usher  Chris Brown以及Trey Songz
将角逐"灵魂/R&B类最受欢迎男歌手奖"
精彩尽在ABC《第40届全美音乐大奖》
由"Case Mate  好马配好鞍"赞助
欢迎回到《第40届全美音乐大奖》
欢迎全美最火二人组新星Florida Georgia Line
她的新专辑"Red"是近十年来
首周销量最高的专辑
一周内售出超过120万
下个月  她将亲临时代广场
参加"新年摇滚夜"的表演
欢迎这位11次AMA赢家
咱们的好妹子
"T-Swizzle"是Taylor Swift别称
"T-Swizzle"  Taylor Swift
♪Once upon a time♪
♪A few mistakes ago♪
♪I was in your sights♪
♪You got me alone♪
♪You found me, you found me, you found me♪
♪I guess you didn't care♪
♪And I guess I liked that♪
♪And when I fell hard♪
♪You took a step back♪
♪Without me, without me, without me♪
♪And he's long gone♪
♪When he's next to me♪
♪And I realize the blame is on me♪
♪'Cause I knew you were trouble when you walked in♪
♪So shame on me now♪
♪Flew me to places I'd never been♪
♪'Til you put me down, oh♪
♪I knew you were trouble when you walked in♪
♪So shame on me now♪
♪Flew me to places I'd never been♪
♪Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground♪
♪Oh, oh, trouble, trouble, trouble♪
♪No apologies♪
♪He'll never see you cry♪
♪Pretend he doesn't know♪
♪That he's the reason why♪
♪You're drowning, you're drowning, you're drowning♪
♪Now I heard you moved on♪
♪From whispers on the street♪
♪A new notch in your belt♪
♪Is all I'll ever be♪
♪And now I see, now I see, now I see♪
♪He was long gone when he met me♪
♪And I realize the joke is on me, hey♪
♪I knew you were trouble when you walked in♪
♪So shame on me now♪
♪Flew me to places I'd never been♪
♪'Til you put me down, oh♪
♪I knew you were trouble when you walked in♪
♪So shame on me now♪
♪Flew me to places I'd never been♪
♪Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground♪
♪Oh, oh, trouble, trouble, trouble♪
♪And the saddest fear comes creeping in♪
♪That you never loved me♪
♪Or her, or anyone, or anything, yeah♪
♪(I knew you were trouble when you walked in)♪
♪So shame on me now♪
♪Flew me to places I'd never been(never been)♪
♪'Til you put me down, oh♪
♪I knew you were trouble when you walked in♪
♪So shame on me now♪
♪Flew me to places I'd never been♪
♪Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground♪
♪Oh, oh, trouble, trouble, trouble♪
♪I knew you were trouble when you walked in♪
♪Trouble, trouble, trouble♪
来自ABC热卖大剧《童话镇》
欢迎Jennifer Morrison及Ginnifer Goodwin
第一位获该奖项的是Stevie Wonder
来看看今年的提名名单
"灵魂/R&B类最受欢迎男歌手奖"
获提名的有
获得全美音乐大奖的是...
Usher
这是Usher第八次获得全美音乐大奖
并且第四次获得该奖项
他已三年蝉联该奖
大家好
我比较健忘
所以我说快一点
创造梦想...梦工厂...梦想
灵魂/R&B类最受欢迎男歌手
可恶  说不出来了
团结让梦想成真
赶紧说完拉倒
但我要感谢我的经理人
[貌似...被消音了]
就是这样
Jean  Amarra  Akika
我的创作团队  Mark Pitts  Rico Love
Natural  Sara
Mika  Tom  Peter
我有忘了谁吗
就算忘了我也不知道
他们让我赶快说完
但我还有些人想感谢
Rico Love
谢谢Virgil Roberts  Kenny Marsalis
我的经纪人团队  DWE
谢谢你们做我坚强的后盾
谢谢颁给我这超赞奖
感谢所有粉丝
感谢你们  我爱你们
接下来将要登场的是Nicki Minaj
以及Linkin Park
不要走开
还有Pink带来不看后悔的精彩表演
谁将获得"年度新人"大奖
Carly Rae Jepsen  One Direction
Gotye  fun.  还是J. Cole
ABC稍后揭晓
《第40届全美音乐奖》  精彩尽在ABC
由全新的道奇Dart赞助播出
道奇  新规
AMA辉煌时刻
♪Time after time♪
♪If your lost♪
♪You can look♪
♪And you will find it♪
♪Time after time♪
♪If you fall♪
♪I will catch you♪
♪I will be waiting♪
♪Time after time♪
他们的节日专辑直接登顶榜单
他们是Lady Antebellum
本奖项的候选者
代表了乡村音乐的后起之秀
他们都在很短的时间内就成为了巨星
来看看三位候选人
"乡村类最受欢迎男歌手"
获得提名的有
获得全美音乐大奖的是...
Luke Bryan
这是Luke Bryan获得的首座全美音乐大奖
今晚他的专辑同样被提名为
"乡村类最受欢迎专辑"
大家好吗
感谢大家
感谢我的妻子让我保持童性
乡村类最受欢迎男歌手
容忍我每周都外出巡演
我爱你宝贝
这是一项由歌迷投票产生的奖项
不知何故
我总与此类奖项有缘
这对我来说意味着一切
感谢上帝  让我得此殊荣
感谢我的歌迷  我的家庭
感谢所有一直支持我的人
感谢Capitol唱片公司
我的经理  Kerry Edwards
谢谢Corn&Cap Shawn
感谢唱片公司Capitol
我的经纪人  Jay Williams
我家中可爱的孩子们
小土豆芽和宝宝  我爱你们
站在这的Lady Antebellum
也是我能获得成功的重要原因
我爱你  乡村音乐电台
我爱我的歌迷  谢谢
欢迎获得"另类摇滚最受欢迎歌手"奖的
Linkin Park
♪The cycle repeated♪
♪As explosions broke in the sky♪
♪All that I needed♪
♪Was the one thing I couldn't find♪
♪And you were there at the turn♪
♪Waiting to let you know♪
♪We're building it up♪
♪To break it back down♪
♪To burn it down♪
♪We can't wait♪
♪To burn it to the ground♪
♪The colors conflicted♪
♪As the flames climbed into the clouds♪
♪I wanted to fix this♪
♪But couldn't stop from tearing it down♪
♪And you were there at the time♪
♪Caught in the burning glow♪
♪And I was there at the turn♪
♪Waiting to let you know♪
♪We're building it up♪
♪To break it back down♪
♪To burn it down♪
♪We can't wait to burn it to the ground♪
♪Told me yes♪
♪Held me high♪
♪I believed when you told that lie♪
♪I played soldier you played king♪
♪Struck me down when I kissed that ring♪
♪You lost that right to hold that crown♪
♪I built you up but you let me down♪
♪So when you fall♪
♪Take my turn♪
♪And fan the flames your blazes burn♪
♪And you were there at the time♪
♪Waiting to let me know♪
♪We're building it up♪
♪To break it back down♪
♪To burn it down♪
♪We can't wait to burn it to the ground♪
♪When you fall♪
♪I take my turn♪
♪Fan the flames as your blazes burn♪
♪We can't wait to burn it to the ground♪
♪When you fall♪
♪I take my turn♪
♪Fan the flames as your blazes burn♪
♪We can't wait to burn it to the ground♪
欢迎Nicki Minaj
首次演唱她的新单曲《Freedom》
♪Don't ever thank me for opening doors♪
♪But they ain't even thank Jesus when he died on a cross♪
♪'Cause your spirit is ungrateful♪
♪Chicks is so hateful I remain a staple♪
♪My career's been a pink print♪
♪When I retire tell 'em think pink♪
♪Pink Friday is the imprint♪
♪And these chicks basic instinct♪
♪Oh snap my commercial's on♪
♪Did I really body bing with commercial songs♪
♪Did I really prophecy everything I do♪
♪But before I continue let me thank my crew♪
♪So that was Young Wayne Mack Maine Baby and Slim came♪
♪Tez and E.I. told me it wouldn't be in vain♪
♪Cause prior to me signing I could've went insane♪
♪And even now I think do I really want this fame♪
♪Let me get up and go 700 to go♪
♪overseas for a show♪
♪Everybody get quiet when I'm starting the show♪
♪Man I'm birthing these artists♪
♪And I'm starting to show♪
♪I feel free♪
♪I feel freedom♪
♪Why dey mad♪
♪You should see dem♪
♪Burn up now♪
♪'Cause it's crazy in here crazy in here crazy in here♪
♪Who I wanna work with nobody♪
♪99 percent of them is nobody♪
♪Baby acting like they killing it okay♪
♪When I check they resumes nobodies♪
♪These dudes is fake yep and opportunists♪
♪They'll spend they last dime to say they copped the soonest♪
♪Why are they going broke to get ye approval♪
♪Pretty soon they'll be back up on 'em ramen noodles♪
♪B-b-b-bible Queen is the title♪
♪And if you are my rival then that means you're suicidal♪
♪And if you in the club then it's the Young Money recital♪
♪I'm just that vital♪
♪I'm busy never idle♪
♪I'm ya idol I'm ya idol I'm ya mother and ya idol♪
♪Pink Friday in Macy's thongs and some pasties♪
♪Yo what other female rapper perfume in here 'cause I must've missed it♪
♪12 milli to kick me feet up get ready this is the re-up(I feel free)♪
♪I feel freedom♪
♪Why dey mad♪
♪You should see dem♪
♪Burn up now♪
♪'Cause it's crazy in here crazy in here crazy in here♪
♪Mirror mirror won't you realize♪
♪I just have to decide♪
♪What you hiding from♪
♪Mirror mirror won't you realize♪
♪I just have to decide what you hiding from♪
♪What you hiding from hiding baby♪
♪Would you would you give ya♪
♪Would you would you give your all for you♪
♪Would you would you give your all for you(I feel free)♪
♪I feel freedom♪
♪Why dey mad (Why dey mad)♪
♪You should see them(You should see them)♪
♪Burn up now♪
♪'Cause it's crazy in here crazy in here crazy in♪
♪I feel free♪
一起来
♪Feel freedom(I feel freedom)♪
♪Why dey mad(Why they mad)♪
♪You should see dem♪
♪Burn up now♪
♪'Cause it's crazy in here crazy in here crazy in here♪
♪It's crazy in here♪
投票已经结束
年度新人/组合
谁会摘得"年度新人"大奖呢
结果马上揭晓
是J. Cole  Fun.  Gotye
Carly Rae Jepsen还是One Direction
接下来Pink  Pitbull
以及Swizz Beatz  Chris Brown
Ludacris的精彩表演尽在下节播出
谁会赢得"年度艺人奖"
是Justin Bieber  Drake
Maroon 5
Katy Perry
还是Rhianna
敬请锁定ABC
欢迎回到洛杉矶诺基亚剧院
有请超模  主持人  制片人和设计师
Heidi Klum
她的每张专辑都大卖
包括最新专辑《The Truth About Love》
她是一位超级巨星  诗人
一位潮女和新晋母亲
怎样用一个词来形容她呢
很简单  她就是Pink
♪Ever wonder about what he's doing♪
♪How it all turned to lies♪
♪Sometimes I think that it's better♪
♪To never ask why♪
♪Where there is desire♪
♪There is gonna be a flame♪
♪Where there is a flame♪
♪Someone's bound to get burned♪
♪But just because it burns♪
♪Doesn't mean you're gonna die♪
♪You've gotta get up and try try try♪
♪Gotta get up and try try try♪
♪You gotta get up and try try try♪
♪Funny how the heart can be deceiving♪
♪More than just a couple times♪
♪Why do we fall in love so easy♪
♪Even when it's not right♪
♪Where there is desire♪
♪There is gonna be a flame♪
♪Where there is a flame♪
♪Someone's bound to get burned♪
♪But just because it burns♪
♪Doesn't mean you're gonna die♪
♪You've gotta get up and try try try♪
♪Gotta get up and try try try♪
♪You gotta get up and try try try♪
♪Ever worried that it might be ruined♪
♪And does it make you wanna cry♪
♪When you're out there doing what you're doing♪
♪Are you just getting by♪
♪Tell me are you just getting by by by♪
♪Where there is desire♪
♪There is gonna be a flame♪
♪Where there is a flame♪
♪Someone's bound to get burned♪
♪But just because it burns♪
♪Doesn't mean you're gonna die♪
♪You've gotta get up and try try try♪
♪You gotta get up and try try try♪
♪Gotta get up and try try try♪
♪You gotta get up♪
♪You gotta get up and try try try♪
下一奖项的颁奖嘉宾是
曾两获AMA奖项的Backstreet Boys
- AMA对我们意义重大  - 没错
我们在这里得过奖也唱过歌
信不信由你  横跨十几年呢
伙计  干嘛把我们说得那么老
今晚我们很荣幸能颁发
"年度新人/组合奖"
欢乐即将洒满人间
AMA奖马上颁出
以下是"年度新人/组合奖"提名
J. Cole
Fun.
Gotye
Carly Rae Jepsen
以及One Direction
"年度新人/组合奖"  获奖的是...
- 手机手机告诉我  - 稍安勿躁
Carly Rae Jepsen
《Call Me Maybe》蝉联榜首九周
现在她获得了"年度新人奖"
这是她的第一次得到全美音乐大奖
非常感谢  谢谢
天啊  太谢谢你们了
我的粉丝们  我真的感激不尽
年度新人/组合
谢谢Jimmy Iovine
和Interscopec唱片公司的所有人
感谢Jonathan和所有Schoolboy唱片公司的人
谢谢Scooter Braun和Justin Bieber
和Schoolboy公司的每一个人
谢谢我的家庭  朋友和男友的支持
这真的太棒了  非常非常感谢
稍后
Justin Bieber与Nicki Minaj同台献唱
还有Christina Aguilera
Pitbull和Carrie Underwood依次登台
并揭晓"乡村类最受欢迎组合"花落谁家
是Lady Antebellum  Rascal Flats
还是Zac Brown Band
让我们拭目以待  精彩尽在ABC
ABC台《第40届全美音乐大奖》
由Old Navy赞助播出
史上最给力折扣尽在此
Cheermageddon  快乐触手可得
欢迎白金唱片销量艺人
Colbie Caillat和Gavin Degraw
- 你今晚美艳动人  - 谢谢夸奖
在颁发"乡村类最受欢迎组合"前
说到合唱
我们下周要在纳什维尔
为《We Both Know》拍摄MV
是的  我很期待
我们植入小广告呢
好了  回归正题
提名人选根据
Mediabase电台统计的无线播放量
- 厉害啊  - 没错
及Big Champagne Media Measurement
提供的歌曲销量得出
ABC官网进行了公投  可供查阅
下面我来向你们介绍
监督颁奖结果的公证员们
他们来自专业权威的安永审计事务所
分别是John Nendick
Marian Cavallaro和Mark Besca
了解了以上内容
一起看看下一奖项的提名情况
以下是"乡村类最受欢迎组合"提名
- 好激动啊  - 是啊  好紧张
获得全美音乐大奖的是...
我们的好友  Lady Antebellum
这是Lady Antebellum音乐生涯中
第三次获得全美音乐大奖
他们2010和2011均获该项奖
这个奖归功于
这一年追随我们巡演的无数粉丝
这是我们首次大型巡演
这是拜你们所赐
感谢Capitol唱片公司的每个人
乡村类最受欢迎组合
感谢我们团队辛苦工作的每个人
这一年来  我们有太多要感恩
这一刻感觉很棒  十分感谢
感谢我的家人和爱人  我爱你宝贝
今年感恩节我会回家
爱你们  谢谢大家
再一次有请
今晚的获奖者Carly Rae Jepsen
一眨眼间
他从才华横溢的新人
成长为一代巨星
有请我的好友  Justin Bieber
♪As long as you love me, yeah♪
♪We're under pressure♪
♪Seven billion people in the world trying to fit in♪
♪Keep it together♪
♪Smile on your face♪
♪Even though your heart is frowning♪
♪But hey now, you know girl♪
♪We both know it's a cruel world♪
♪But I will take my chances♪
♪As long as you love me♪
♪We could be starving♪
♪We could be homeless♪
♪We could be broke♪
♪As long as you love me♪
♪I'll be your platinum♪
♪I'll be your silver♪
♪I'll be your gold♪
♪As long as you love me♪
♪As long as you love me, love me♪
♪I don't know if this makes sense♪
♪But you're my hallelujah♪
♪Give me a time and place, and I'll rendezvous♪
♪And I'll fly you to it, I'll beat ya there♪
♪Girl you know I got you♪
♪When us trust♪
♪A couple of things I can't spell without you♪
♪Now we are on top of the world♪
♪'Cause that's just how we do♪
♪Used to tell me sky's the limit♪
♪Now the sky's our point of view♪
♪Man now we stepping out like wow oh god♪
♪Camera's pointed shoot♪
♪Ask me what's my best side♪
♪I stand back and point at you you♪
♪You the one that I argue with♪
♪I feel like I need a new girl to be bothered♪
♪But the grass ain't always greener on the other side♪
♪It's green where you water it♪
♪So I know we got issues baby true true true♪
♪But I'd rather work on this with you♪
♪Than to go ahead and start with someone new♪
♪As long as you love me♪
♪We could be starving♪
♪We could be homeless♪
♪We could be broke♪
♪As long as you love me♪
♪I'll be your platinum♪
♪I'll be your silver♪
♪I'll be your gold♪
♪As long as you love me♪
♪As long as you love me, you love me♪
♪You love me yeah♪
♪As long as you love me yeah♪
♪As long as you love me yeah, oh baby♪
站起来  大家一起来
我让你们站起来
一起来
♪Show you off♪
♪Tonight I wanna show you off♪
♪What you got♪
♪A billion could've never bought♪
♪We gonna party like it's 3012 tonight♪
♪I wanna show you all the finer things in life♪
♪So just forget about the world♪
♪Be young tonight♪
♪I'm coming for ya I'm coming for ya♪
♪'Cause all I need♪
♪Is a beauty and a beat♪
♪Who can make my life complete♪
♪It's all about you♪
♪When the music makes you move♪
♪Baby do it like you do♪
♪'Cause yo♪
♪Body rock♪
♪I wanna feel your body rock♪
♪Take a bow♪
♪You on the hottest ticket now♪
♪We gonna party like it's 3012 tonight♪
♪I wanna show you all the finer things in life♪
♪So just forget about the world♪
♪Be young tonight♪
♪I'm coming for ya, I'm coming for ya♪
♪'Cause all I need♪
♪Is a beauty and a beat♪
♪Who can make my life complete♪
♪It's all about you♪
♪When the music makes you move♪
♪Baby do it like you do♪
♪In time, ink lines♪
♪Bitches couldn't get on my incline♪
♪World tour, it's mine♪
♪Ten little letters, on a big sign♪
♪Justin Bieber♪
♪You know I'mma hit 'em with the ether♪
♪Buns out, weiner♪
♪But I gotta keep my eye out for Selener♪
♪Beauty, beauty and the beat♪
♪Beauty from the east♪
♪Beautiful confessions of the priest♪
♪Beast, beauty from the streets♪
♪We don't get deceased♪
♪Every time a beauty on the beats♪
♪Yeah, yeah, yeah (body rock)♪
♪Let's go, let's go♪
♪'Cause all I need♪
♪Is a beauty and a beat♪
♪Who can make my life complete♪
♪It's all about you♪
♪When the music makes you move♪
♪Baby do it like you do♪
♪'Cause♪
下面有请
热门剧《幸福终点站》的女明星
和R&B当红女歌手
Elisha Cuthber以及Kelly Rowland
EDM是音乐中最火辣的新元素
可能你还不知道EDM是什么
它就是"电子舞曲"
这是个全新的奖项
承认了这个
日益重要的音乐类型的地位
下面是首次竞争该奖项的艺人名单
以下是"电子舞曲类最佳艺人"提名
"电子舞曲类最佳艺人"  获奖的是...
David Guetta
感谢大家为他起立鼓掌
但他现在还在巴西
进行全球电子舞曲巡演
但请看大屏幕
David Guetta从里约热内卢发来感谢
我太高兴  太荣幸了
太感谢了
这是《全美音乐大奖》有史以来
第一个电子音乐奖
真心是件大事
看见电子音乐在美国
被大众承认真是太棒了
超级感谢所有粉丝
今晚我没法和你们在一起
因为我还在巴西巡演
马上要上台了
但我非常高兴
我想和所有DJ  制作人
推广员  所有电子舞曲的功臣分享这个奖
还有我的唱片公司Capitol
爱你们哟
♪I got scared when she started to yell♪
AMA辉煌时刻
♪So I handed her my wallet and ran like hell♪
♪I was duckin through alleys right and left♪
♪But when the cops caught up♪
♪They almost beat me to death♪
♪I was arrested charged with agrivated assault♪
♪Yo Clancy we got him♪
♪But it wasn't my fault♪
♪Nevertheless don't mean to bust your bubble♪
♪But girls of the world ain't nothing but trouble♪
♪So next time a girl gives you the play♪
♪Just remember my rhyme and get the hell away♪
广告之后  Pitbull献上表演
稍后
Stevie Wonder向Dick Clark深情致敬
还有Justin Bieber  Drake
Maroon 5  Katy Perry和Rihanna
为"年度艺人奖"进行激烈争夺
精彩尽在ABC
♪Bye, bye, bye♪
AMA辉煌时刻
♪I don't wanna be a fool for you♪
♪Just another player in your game for two♪
♪You may hate me but it ain't no lie♪
♪Bye, bye, bye♪
♪I don't really want to make it tough♪
♪I just wanna tell you that I had enough♪
♪Might sound crazy but it ain't no lie♪
♪Baby, bye, bye, bye♪
现在上台的
是本音乐大奖的宠儿
有请Gloria Estefan
接下来这位歌手
一直享有当代最佳歌手的美誉
她对自己的新专辑更是精益求精
想要以此激励新一代艺人
也确实达到了目的
请掌声欢迎Christina Aguilera
♪Songbird, rebirth, unearth creature♪
♪Submerge from hurt, pain, broken pieces♪
♪Emergency, heartbeat increases♪
♪Rise up lotus, rise, this is the beginning♪
♪(This is the beginning)♪
♪And now the lotus rises (rises rises)♪
♪We are never dying (dying dying)♪
♪Forever flying (flying flying)♪
♪And always surviving♪
♪To the sky, I rise♪
♪Spread my wings, and fly♪
♪I leave the past behind♪
♪And say goodbye♪
♪To the scared child inside♪
♪I sing for freedom, and for love♪
♪I look at my reflection♪
♪Embrace the woman I've become♪
♪The unbreakable lotus in me♪
♪I now set free♪
♪I've been standing where you left me (left me)♪
♪Praying that you'd come and get me (get me)♪
♪But now I've found my second wind (wind)♪
♪Now I found my second skin (skin)♪
♪Well I know what you were thinking♪
♪You thought you'd watch me fade away (away)♪
♪When you broke me into pieces♪
♪But I gave each piece a name (a name)♪
♪One of me is wiser♪
♪One of me is stronger♪
♪One of me's a fighter♪
♪And there's a thousand faces of me♪
♪And we're gonna rise up♪
♪Yeah, we're gonna rise up♪
♪For every time you broke me♪
♪Well you're gonna face an army♪
♪Army of me♪
♪So how does it feel♪
♪To know that I beat you♪
♪That I can defeat you♪
♪Oh how does it feel♪
♪Cause it sure feels sweeter♪
♪It sure feels sweeter than mine♪
♪Now that I am wiser♪
♪Now that I am stronger♪
♪Now that I'm a fighter♪
♪Well you're gonna face an army♪
♪Army of me♪
今夜是属于所有人的庆典
是一场革命
大家一起来
大声喊出来
♪Let there be love♪
♪Here in the, here in the dark♪
♪Turning me, turning me on♪
♪Like I won't fight anymore♪
♪Cause I want your touch, let's go♪
♪Let there be love♪
♪Here in the, here in the dark♪
♪Turning me, turning me on♪
♪Like I won't fight anymore♪
♪Cause I want your touch, let's go♪
♪Let there be love♪
♪Here in the, here in the dark♪
♪Turning me, turning me on♪
♪Like I won't fight anymore♪
♪Cause I want your touch♪
谢谢
他的歌曲动感十足
他的音乐价值连城
有请嗨翻全场的Pitbull
♪ L.A. Latino♪
♪You don't get them girls loose loose♪
♪You don't get the world loose loose♪
♪You don't get money move move♪
♪But I do I do♪
♪I said y'all having a good time out there♪
♪Yeah, yeah, que no pare la fiesta♪
♪Don't stop the party♪
♪I'm running through the world♪
♪Like I'm running back yeah♪
♪Scarface, world's mine, running back yeah♪
♪30,000 people went here on me♪
♪30,000 people in London Wembley♪
♪80,000 people Morocco♪
♪And I'm just getting warmed up, papo♪
♪Catch me with red♪
♪One in Stockholm, Beirut♪
♪Cafe getting my drink on, mole♪
♪We're how to put the women, here the hooka♪
♪All of them sweet, azucar, azucar♪
♪Dale disfruta, dale disfruta♪
♪They can't, they won't♪
♪They never will, stop the party♪
♪I said y'all having a good time out there♪
♪Yeah, yeah, que no pare la fiesta♪
♪Don't stop the party♪
♪I'm from the city, where they stress♪
♪And they sleep real bad♪
♪And now I'm doing shows in Helsinki♪
♪I know what ya'll thinking, you're thinking♪
♪That you can outhiking, but you can't frankly♪
♪I'm out for the benchies, frankies, chinos♪
♪Just cause you ain't me, don't hate me♪
♪As a matter fact you should thank me♪
♪Even if you don't, joel come yankees♪
♪Zig-a zig-a zig-a zig-a♪
♪Who got the key of the world, now, yours truly♪
♪They can't, they won't♪
♪They never will, stop the party♪
♪I said y'all having a good time out there♪
♪Yeah, yeah, que no pare la fiesta♪
♪Don't stop the party♪
♪I'mma give it to ya, ah ah♪
♪Now give it to me, ah ah♪
♪Get funky, get funky♪
♪Now stop♪
♪I said, y'all having a good time out there♪
♪Yeah, yeah, que no pare la fiesta♪
♪Don't stop the party♪
♪Ask for money, and get it viced♪
♪Ask for advice, get money twice♪
♪I'm from the Dirty, but that chico nice♪
♪Ya'll call it a moment, I call it life♪
尽情欢呼吧
让我们重返80年代
♪Mr Worldwide♪
♪Christina Aguilera♪
♪I just wanna♪
一起来
♪I just wanna feel this moment♪
广告过后  超级巨星Carrie Underwood将登场表演
稍后揭晓  谁将赢得年度最佳艺人
年度艺人
Justin Bieber
Drake
Maroon 5
Katy Perry
还是Rihanna
谁会是音乐界的下个传奇  敬请锁定
《第40届全美音乐大奖》  精彩尽在ABC
由三星Galaxy Note II赞助播出
下一代辉煌  由我们创造
我不得不选你了  Britney
AMA辉煌时刻
既然你坐在Justin的大腿上
那我要去坐Britney的大腿
Britney  你妈妈在哪
- 我是唯一...  - 等等
- 我是唯一坐在Britney腿上的主持人
Britney  别缠着我了
肯定在场下某处
我们还是赶紧开奖吧
他搬到纳什维尔后成为一代巨星
纳什维尔  美国乡村音乐中心
而她将在时报广场
和Ryan Seacrest一起主持跨年演唱会
掌声欢迎今晚的的赢家
Luke Bryan以及Jenny McCarthy
你们即将看到的是
"流行/摇滚类最佳专辑"提名名单
获奖专辑将会与历届赢家一起载入史册
其中包括Michael Jackson的《Thriller》
以及Bruce Springsteen的 《Born In The USA》
- 都是杰出的专辑  对吧  - 都很牛
请看大屏幕
以下是"流行/摇滚类最佳专辑"提名
获得全美音乐大奖的是...
Justin Bieber
这是Justin Bieber今晚获得的第二个奖项
他已经获得了六项全美音乐大奖
并且他还是今晚"年度最佳艺人"的候选人
恭喜你  哥们
等一下等一下  我帮你擦擦
我觉得被吃豆腐了
首先  刚刚我在台上忘记感谢
我的贵人Usher Raymond
因为他一直...
我很乐意向你们讲述细节
流行/摇滚类最佳专辑
但那得花掉整晚的时间
此外  我想感谢IDJ公司的团队成员
再次感谢我的家人
我的爸爸妈妈弟弟妹妹
再次感谢我的粉丝们
感谢上帝
没有他  我就不会站在这里
谢谢  我爱你们
我们做到了
兄弟  对不住啦
- 抱歉  我...  - 我也干了
- "疼爱"了他一下  - 忍不住想咬一口
短短七年间
她从一位颇具潜力的乡村歌手
成长为专辑销量一百五十万的巨星
她说  在这段狂野旅途中
她日行千里
因此  快给她让路吧
她就是Carrie Underwood
♪Two black Cadillacs driving in a slow parade♪
♪Headlights shining bright in the middle of the day♪
♪One is for his wife♪
♪The other for the woman who loved him at night♪
♪Two black Cadillacs meeting for the first time♪
♪And the preacher said he was a good man♪
♪And his brother said he was a good friend♪
♪But the women in the two black veils didn't bother to cry♪
♪(Bye, Bye Bye, Bye)♪
♪Yeah they took turns laying a rose down♪
♪Threw a handful of dirt into the deep ground♪
♪He's not the only one who had a secret to hide♪
♪Bye bye, bye bye, bye bye♪
♪(Two black Cadillacs, two black Cadillacs)♪
♪Two months ago his wife called the number on his phone♪
♪It turns out he'd been lying to both of them for so long♪
♪They decided then♪
♪He'd never get away with doing this to them♪
♪Two black Cadillacs waiting for the right time, right time♪
♪And the preacher said he was a good man♪
♪And his brother said he was a good friend♪
♪But the women in the two black veils didn't bother to cry♪
♪(Bye bye, Bye bye)♪
♪Yeah they took turns laying a rose down♪
♪Threw a handful of dirt into the deep ground♪
♪He's not the only one who had a secret to hide♪
♪Bye bye, bye bye, bye bye♪
♪It was the first and the last time they saw each other face to face♪
♪They shared a crimson smile and just walked away♪
♪And left the secret at the grave♪
♪And the preacher said he was a good man♪
♪And his brother said he was a good friend♪
♪But the women in the two black veils they didn't bother to cry♪
♪(Bye bye, Bye bye)♪
♪Yeah they took turns laying a rose down♪
♪Threw a handful of dirt into the deep ground♪
♪He's not the only one who had a secret to hide♪
♪Bye bye, bye bye, bye bye♪
♪Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
接下来出场的是Swiss Beats和特邀嘉宾
Chris Brown还有Ludacris
以及Stevie Wonder的致敬Dick Clark特别表演
还有压轴鸟叔的超级神曲《江南style》
还将颁发"年度艺人"大奖
精彩尽在ABC电视台
下一位出场嘉宾是大热歌手
她的最新专辑刚刚登上排行榜榜首
欢迎Brandy
我把最新专辑命名为《2·11》是有来由的
因为我一直都记得二月十一号
我们失去歌坛永恒天籁的那一天
我们永远不会忘怀  Whitney Houston
女士们先生们  有请Whitney Houston
AMA辉煌时刻
首先我想感谢赐予我力量的伟大的上帝
感谢我的父母
非常感谢你们  我爱你们
真的非常感谢
谢谢
不知道你想表达什么
保佑你  谢谢
♪I have nothing ♪
♪Nothing♪
♪If I don't have you♪
我们爱你  Whitney
他是杰出的嘻哈歌手  制作人
他带了几个名人朋友一起来
有请Swizz Beatz
以及我家Chris Brown和Ludacris
♪Now♪
♪Everyday is your birthday and I hit the floor♪
♪Hi-hit the floor♪
♪I said hit the floor♪
♪Everyday is your birthday and I hit the floor♪
♪Hi-hit the floor♪
♪Let's work♪
♪Watcha think you doing in here♪
♪Girl I got 100 bottles of that Rozay♪
♪Hoes they always be in my ear♪
♪Girl I got a problem solver♪
♪Lean back and swallow♪
♪Make this liquor all dissapear♪
♪Drop it, Drop it♪
♪This your chance girl♪
♪Money all in my pants girl♪
♪It's your night so♪
♪Now♪
♪Everyday is your birthday now hit the floor♪
♪Everyday is your birthday now hit the floor (It's your night girl)♪
♪Hit hit the floor, I say hit the floor♪
♪Everyday is your birthday now hit the floor♪
♪Hit hit the floor, I say hit the floor (Leggo)♪
♪This goes out to the 305's♪
♪718's I mean all the states♪
♪Came back man with the drop top♪
♪You better call the cops♪
♪Baby girl, just stop♪
♪This white chain, ice♪
♪This turing on the bad stuff♪
♪Man we on the floor all night♪
♪She wanna go crazy and plus dance like a white girl♪
♪Told you before it's me bitch♪
♪Y'all talk to much Y'all might be snitches♪
♪I don't do the dirty work, yeah I do the dishes♪
♪I just play with and count my digits♪
♪Get up, get up♪
♪Bring it back, I could bug out, go crazy, I'm out of my mind♪
♪Got Ciroq on deck, got Patron on deck♪
♪Y'all crazy man you ...♪
♪All on the floor with the spandex on♪
♪She got the red bottoms on, man she get it on♪
♪Man I get it on, I just get it on with the best of flow♪
♪Parties in your glass you fill it up until you hit the roof♪
♪Now hit the dancefloor that liquid courage always got you♪
♪Throw your hands up in the air♪
♪Like I'm the life of the party party♪
♪Luda! (Now dance like a white girl)♪
♪I don't know what be♪
♪She dancing too but she killing that beer♪
♪She acting like a white girl drunk♪
♪And she outta control but I'm feeling that yeah♪
♪Drop it like you owe it to me♪
♪Give it to me like it's mine in the first place♪
♪Lady in the street, freaky in the bed♪
♪Wild in the party, professional in the workplace♪
♪She independent and sexy I think I love her man (I love)♪
♪She keep it clean but get messy under the cover man♪
♪Dirty yeah you know it clap your hands♪
♪If you dirty and you know it clap your hands♪
♪She know how to do it like♪
♪She the one who taught the class♪
♪That thing so I need somewhere to it is my class♪
♪I got a million uses and I get all the the excluss♪
♪And that body so ruthless♪
♪Parties in your glass♪
♪You full it up until you hit the roof♪
♪Now hit the dance floor that♪
♪Liquid courage always got you♪
♪Throw your hands up in the air♪
♪Like I'm the life of the party party♪
♪Just lance♪
♪Let's work♪
♪Hit the floor♪
♪Every day is your birthday now hit the floor♪
♪Hit hit the floor, I say hit the floor♪
♪Let's work♪
♪Happy birthday AMA♪
她是大热剧集《下一站歌后》的领衔主演
他则是一直红透半边天的说唱歌手
让我们有请
Hayden Panettiere和50 Cent
下面这个奖项可谓群雄逐鹿
所以赢家可能是男歌手
也可能是女歌手
去年  一名女歌手捧走奖杯
让我们拭目以待今晚她能否卫冕
如果不能  看看男歌手们能否争口气
说的是
"说唱/嘻哈类最受欢迎歌手"奖
以下是提名
"说唱/嘻哈类最受欢迎歌手"
得奖者是...
提名的三个歌手均曾属于此唱片公司
Young Money娱乐公司
Nicki Minaj
这是Nicki Minaj今晚的第二座奖杯
此前在"说唱/嘻哈最佳专辑奖"中
拔得头筹
一共获得四座"全美音乐大奖"奖杯
♪男人们  奖我又拿走了♪
♪男人们  只有我最牛♪
刚才得奖已经让我语无伦次了
说唱/嘻哈类最受欢迎歌手
我的鸡汤们呢
在那儿吗
鸡汤们  我知道你们正在看节目
我爱你们
你们的热情一直激励着我
感谢你们每个人的投票
我真想抱抱你们  亲亲你们
跟你们亲密接触一番
我要感谢每一个帮助我
走上成功之路的人
我最好的朋友今天也来了
还有  我从来没感谢过我的发型师
Terrance  就是你
我太爱你了
谢谢你一直陪伴着我
宝贝之前给我发短信说
Young Money的人都在家看直播
我爱你们
我坚信忠诚跟友情
谢谢你  Wayne
谢谢你给我的这个机会
《Pink Friday》这张专辑
今晚午夜就在各大唱片店开售
《Freedom》的MV明天发布哦
爱你们  鸡汤们
还有  感谢全美音乐大奖
你们一直以来都非常优秀
我知道自己说的话被切掉了
但还是要说我爱你们  谢谢
接下来
Stevie Wonder将为Dick Clark
献上感人肺腑的致辞
鸟叔将携手国际巨星
表演《江南Style》
以及Justin Bieber  Drake
Maroon 5  Katy Perry和Rihanna
将角逐"年度艺人"大奖
欢迎继续收看《全美音乐大奖》
他们是来自犹他州的摇滚乐团
让我们欢迎Neon Trees
"乡村类最受欢迎专辑"奖
可能是今晚最独特的一项
如果Lionel Richie赢了的话
他将成为全美音乐大奖历史上
第一个包揽"流行/摇滚类"
"灵魂/R&B类"
还有"乡村音乐类"奖项的人
不过竞争相当激烈
让我们拭目以待
获得"乡村类最受欢迎专辑"奖
提名的有
得奖的是...
Carrie Underwood
这是Carrie Underwood的
第七次全美音乐大奖提名
以及第四次获得此奖项
这意味着她发行的每一张专辑
都获得了这个奖项
不可思议
太感谢你们了
这对我来说太重要了
这张专辑是我引以为傲的心血
乡村类最受欢迎专辑
我要感谢上帝
赐予我音乐上源源不断的灵感
才得以创作这张专辑
感谢我热情的粉丝们
当我在创作《Blown Away》时
一直都陪伴着我
这是我最享受人生的一刻
亲们  我爱你们
谢谢我的家人们  朋友们
粉丝们还有各大音乐电台
靠着你们我才能吃饭
上帝保佑你们
谢谢你们
女士们先生们  再次有请
Ryan Seacrest
和你们一样
我也曾是Dick Clark的超级粉丝
我总是被他的星范儿
和面对镜头时的气场
深深地折服
尽管后来我与他和他的妻子
Carrie成为了好友
也不妨碍我从心底深深崇拜着他
他真是个很棒的出品人
历经40年的洗礼后
这个节目仍保留了Dick最初的风格
让全球顶级的歌手
齐聚一堂  公平竞争
就让音乐传达这一切吧
Dick热爱音乐的力量
它能给人们带来纯粹的愉悦
所以今晚我们要用音乐
来缅怀这位伟人的美好人生
下面  有请49年来
Dick一直喜爱的歌手兼挚友
女士们先生们
有请伟大的Stevie Wonder
大家好  爱你们
首先我想缅怀Dick Clark
我记得13岁时
与他在费城初遇
摩城是最大的黑人唱片企业
在摩城巡演时  演唱《Fingertips》
以及《All the Things That Happened》
我记得和他在全美音乐大奖
感受到他的友善和关爱
记得他对音乐的热爱和对人类的博爱
今晚  我想对那些在乎的人们说
我呼吁那些媒体人  领导者
政治家  未来领袖
请献出你们的爱
就像在我们歌手的心中音乐至上
让全世界团结在一起
飚舞到天亮吧
走起
来吧
嗨起来
♪Everyone's feeling pretty♪
♪It's hotter than July♪
♪Though the world's full of problems♪
♪They couldn't touch us even if they tried♪
♪From the park I hear rhythms♪
♪Marley's hot on the box♪
♪Tonight there will be a party♪
♪On the corner at the end of the block♪
♪Didn't know you would be jammin'♪
♪Until the break of dawn♪
♪I bet you nobody ever told you♪
♪That you would be jammin' until the break of dawn♪
♪You may as well believe what you are feeling♪
♪Because you feel your body jammin'♪
♪You would be jammin' and jammin' and jammin'♪
♪Jammin' and jammin' and jammin' and jammin'♪
会就跟着唱
♪My Cherie Amour♪
♪Lovely as a summer's day♪
♪My Cherie Amour, distant as the milky way♪
♪My Cherie Amour, pretty little one that I adore♪
♪You're the only girl my heart beats for♪
♪How I wish that you were mine♪
大家一起唱
一起来
一起唱
来吧
♪Music is a world within itself♪
♪With a language we all understand♪
♪With an equal opportunity♪
♪For all to sing dance and clap their hands♪
♪For there's Basie, Miller, Sachimo♪
♪And the king of all Sir Duke♪
♪And with a voice like Ella's ringing out♪
♪There's no way the band can lose♪
♪You can feel it all over♪
♪You can feel it all over people♪
♪You can…♪
大家唱起来   嗨起来
上帝保佑你  唱起来
他捧回23座AMA奖杯
是史上荣获AMA奖项最多的人
今年我们庆祝他的《Bad》专辑发行25周年
他就是Michael Jackson
AMA辉煌时刻
女士们先生们
有请独一无二的Michael Jackson
Michael Jackson
很开心赢得奖项
我会永远珍爱它
赢得奖项我感觉好荣幸
千言万语道不出我此刻的心情
感谢你们
我就像给他打杂的
爱你们哦
爱你们
欢迎回到《全美音乐大奖》现场
艺人  作词家  制作人
还有音乐领军人
欢迎will.i.am
今晚最后一个奖项
也是今晚的重头戏
"年度艺人"
这个奖诞生于1996年
当年被Garth Brooks捧回家
今晚将花落谁家呢
以下是"年度艺人"提名
"年度艺人"  获奖的是...
Justin Bieber
这已经是Justin Bieber
第七次获得全美音乐大奖
同时也是今晚第三次获奖
这是我妈妈
她很纤细  但很美
非常感谢您
首先  我想说...
他们告诉我...
年度艺人
我都没法思考了  太激动了
谢谢您一直相信我
我要感谢...每一个人
这太不可思议了
我都不知道该说些什么了
我只想说...一路上的成长很艰辛
一直以来大家都关注着我
我只是...想说
只要你们始终相信我
我永远不会...
我会一直让你们骄傲的  我会的
非常感谢大家  我爱你们
大家先别着急坐下
唯一的理由是...
我们中的许多人都会上传视频到Youtube
但只有一个人能够在
短短几个月里获得7亿点击率
来自韩国的奇葩男子
有请亲爱的鸟叔  尖叫吧
恭喜今晚所有的获奖者
这里是《第40届全美音乐大奖》颁奖礼
祝各位晚安
七个全美音乐大奖未通过直播宣布
成人时代最受欢迎歌手  Adele
当代最具影响艺人  tobyMac
拉丁类最受欢迎歌手  Shakira
流行/摇滚类最受欢迎组合  Maroon 5
流行/摇滚类最受欢迎女歌手  Katy Perry
灵魂/R&B类最佳专辑  Rihanna  《Talk That Talk》
灵魂/R&B类最受欢迎女歌手  Beyoncé
提名依据来自
Mediabase电台和索闻媒体平台
所提供的电台信息
以及Big Champagne网站
所提供的音乐购买信息
观众们可以在ABC.com上进行投票
投票数据由永安公司统计且
投票结果在宣布获奖前始终保密
嘉宾的往返机票由美国航空公司提供
美国航空公司的航班遍布
全世界40个国家250个城市
今晚的典礼非常精彩
而明早的《早安美国》将带您揭秘
今晚《全美音乐大奖》的幕后故事
周二《早安美国》将为您带来
Nicki Minaj的直播表演
精彩尽在ABC
♪哥是江南Style♪
♪오빤 강남스타일♪
♪江南Style♪
♪강남스타일♪
♪白天是个温暖的有人情味的女人♪
♪낮에는 따사로운 인간적인 여자♪
♪懂得享受一杯咖啡的惬意的有品女人♪
♪커피 한잔의 여유를 아는 품격 있는 여자♪
♪等夜幕降临内心就热烈澎湃的女人♪
♪밤이 오면 심장이 뜨거워지는 여자♪
♪如此有反差的女人♪
♪그런 반전 있는 여자♪
大家一起来
♪我是个男子汉♪
♪나는 사나이♪
♪白天像你一样温暖的那种男子汉♪
♪낮에는 너만큼 따사로운 그런 사나이♪
♪等不及咖啡变凉就一口闷的男子汉♪
♪커피 식기도 전에 원샷 때리는 사나이♪
♪等夜幕降临心脏就狂野到要爆掉的男子汉♪
♪밤이 오면 심장이 터져버리는 사나이♪
♪那种男子汉♪
♪그런 사나이♪
♪美丽的人  可爱的人啊♪
♪아름다워 사랑스러워♪
♪没错  你 Hey 没错  就是你  Hey♪
♪그래 너 hey 그래 바로 너 hey♪
♪美丽的人  可爱的人啊♪
♪아름다워 사랑스러워♪
♪没错  你  Hey 没错  就是你  Hey♪
♪그래 너 hey 그래 바로 너 hey♪
♪现在起让我们放纵到底♪
♪지금부터 갈 데까지 가볼까♪
该怎么做
♪哥是江南Style♪
♪오빤 강남스타일♪
♪江南Style♪
♪강남스타일♪
♪OH OH OH OH OH  哥是江南Style♪
♪옵옵옵옵옵  오빤 강남스타일♪
♪江南Style♪
♪강남스타일♪
♪OH OH OH OH OH  哥是江南Style♪
♪옵옵옵옵옵  오빤 강남스타일♪
♪Eh- Sexy Lady♪
♪OH OH OH OH OH  哥是江南Style♪
♪옵옵옵옵옵  오빤 강남스타일♪
♪Eh- Sexy Lady♪
♪OH OH OH OH OH♪
♪옵옵옵옵옵♪
♪表面挺贤淑  放纵时又能High的女人♪
♪정숙해 보이지만 놀 땐 노는 여자♪
♪觉得时候到了  就会松开发髻的女人♪
♪이때다 싶으면 묶었던 머리 푸는 여자♪
♪穿得严实  却比裸着更具性感的女人♪
♪가렸지만 웬만한 노출보다 야한 여자♪
♪就是那种带感的女人♪
♪그런 감각적인 여자♪
♪我是男子汉♪
♪나는 사나이♪
♪表面挺斯文  放纵时又能High的男子汉♪
♪점잖아 보이지만 놀 땐 노는 사나이♪
♪等到时机到来便会彻底发狂的男子汉♪
♪때가 되면 완전 미쳐버리는 사나이♪
♪没有肌肉疙瘩却头脑强悍的男子汉♪
♪근육보다 사상이 울퉁불퉁한 사나이♪
♪那种男子汉♪
♪그런 사나이♪
♪美丽的人  可爱的人啊♪
♪아름다워 사랑스러워♪
♪没错  你  Hey 没错  就是你 Hey♪
♪그래 너 hey 그래 바로 너 hey♪
♪美丽的人  可爱的人啊♪
♪아름다워 사랑스러워♪
♪没错  你  Hey  没错  就是你  Hey♪
♪그래 너 hey 그래 바로 너 hey♪
♪现在起让我们放纵到底♪
♪지금부터 갈 데까지 가볼까♪
来点掌声
Psy
Hammer大驾光临
♪哥是江南Style♪
♪오빤강남스타일♪
♪Too legit♪
♪Too legit to quit (Gangnam Style)♪
♪Too legit to quit♪
♪Eh- Sexy Lady♪
♪Keep up, keep up. Keep up keep up keep up♪
♪Keep up, keep up♪
♪Keep up up up♪
♪Too legit, too legit to quit♪
♪Too too too too legit to quit♪
♪Too legit♪
♪Too legit to quit♪
♪Too too too too legit to quit♪
AMA  欢呼吧
♪哥是江南Style♪
♪오빤강남스타일♪
♪Eh- Sexy Lady♪
♪OH OH OH OH OH  哥是江南Style♪
♪옵옵옵옵옵 오빤강남스타일♪
♪Eh- Sexy Lady♪
♪OH OH OH OH OH♪
♪옵옵옵옵옵♪
♪哥是江南Style♪
♪오빤강남스타일♪
♪Too legit♪
♪Too legit to quit (Gangnam Style)♪
♪Eh- Sexy Lady♪
♪Keep up, keep up. Keep up keep up keep up♪
♪Keep up, keep up♪
♪Keep up up up♪
♪Gang-gang-gang time♪